

CONTACT ME AT

Badalona

christian_8_neus@hotmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ christian-hernandez-heras/

https://github.com/Christian2497

610093477

SKILLS SUMMARY

MongoDB

React

JavaScript

CSS

HTML5

Express

LANGUAGES

English | Medium

Catalan | Native

Spanish | Native

CHRISTIAN HERNÁNDEZ

WEB DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Hi! I am Christian Hernández and I want to be a great Front-End Developer.

I have great skills with React (especially with JavaScript), although currently I continue to gain knowledge to continue training and continue learning to improve my work experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelancer

Present

 Developing personal projects in some areas that need to improve.

Internship specialist in a gym

Implika | Sept 2019 - Dec 2019

- Helped new clients show them how to operate the gym.
- Gave TRX and GAP classes.

Preventive Computer Technician

INET | Sept 2017 - Jul 2018

- Fix computer problems.
- Provide maintenance for computer problems.
- Update the computer system.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

• Web Developer
Ironhack | Sept 2020 - Dec 2020

• Fitness and Nutrition Trainer

Implika | Sept 2019 - Sept 2020

Video game design and development

DEUSTO | Sept 2018 - Ago 2019

• Higher Degree in Computer Science

Cultural Badalona | Sept 2016 - Jun 2017